Guide to the Bernard Wolfe Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 1999 Acquisition, 1920s-1961; 2.25; (3 boxes)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1949, undated (Box 12)
  - Carbon papers, undated (Box 12)
  - "Public Voucher for Purchases and Services other than Personal", 1944 June (Box 12)
  - "Veterans' Authors' Workshop", undated (Box 12)
  - Scrapbook, undated (Box 13 (Oversize))
- January 2003 Acquisition, undated; 0.21; (1 box)
  The January 2003 Acquisition consists of photocopies of fiction and other writings by Wolfe that appeared in Playboy magazine during the 1960s.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 441.
  Gift of Albert Wolfe, 2003.
  - Writings (photocopies), undated; 2 (Box 14)